theoptionsguide.com 2010-11-28

# The Options Guide - Privacy Policy

| 

TheOptionsGuide.com understands that the privacy and security of information that is gathered and used on our website is important to our users. We want you to be comfortable as you explore our site, and participate in its interactive nature. We are committed to providing an online environment that is both Private and Secure by adhering to confidentiality standards that are designed to protect our visitors' personal information. TheOptionsGuide.com has created this Privacy Policy Statement to demonstrate our commitment to the protection of your privacy.

### Personal Data

Most of the information provided by TheOptionsGuide.com is offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. For instance, you can search our site for options strategies without giving out any personally identifiable information.

### General Data

TheOptionsGuide.com uses a variety of Internet technologies which help us to manage our site operations and track website usage behavior so that we can customize information and advertisements to make your visits more enjoyable and meaningful. These Internet technologies include: 

  * IP Addresses: random numbers assigned to individual computers which TheOptionsGuide.com uses to administer our Web site and help diagnose problems with our servers.
  * Web Beacons (sometimes called single-pixel Gifs): electronic images that allow TheOptionsGuide.com to count users who have visited certain Web pages we wish to track. For example, Web Beacons may also be placed by our advertising partners on TheOptionsGuide.com's Web pages to help determine the effectiveness of Internet advertising campaigns.
  * Cookies: small electronic files transferred from our Web site to your hard drive. Cookies enable TheOptionsGuide.com to recognize repeat visitors, track usage behavior and facilitate your access to and use of our site. If you wish, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a Cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all Cookies. If you turn Cookies off, however, you won't have access to many of the features which make your experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Links to a third party site

Our web site provides links to other web sites. Please be aware that when you click on one of these links, you are going to another web site even though the TheOptionsGuide.com logo or banner may still be visible. Information you enter on these other web sites is being collected by that site, not TheOptionsGuide.com. Please read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their Privacy Policy Statement may differ from ours. TheOptionsGuide.com does not control such sites, and therefore, is not responsible for their contents. TheOptionsGuide.com's inclusion of hyperlinks to these sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites or any association with their operators. While TheOptionsGuide.com strive to protect our visitors' information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you disclose such information at your own risk.

### Is my Personal information Secure?

TheOptionsGuide.com works hard to ensure that our systems are secure and that they meet industry standards. Where appropriate, we employ firewalls, encryption technology, user access codes (e.g., userIDs and passwords to enter account holder areas) and other access control mechanisms to control access to systems and data. Even with these security measures, we cannot guarantee that your communications with our site will never be unlawfully intercepted, or that your personal information will never be unlawfully accessed by third parties. Your password should never be shared with anyone. TheOptionsGuide.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e-mail. We will continue to assess new technology to evaluate its ability to provide additional protection of your personal information.

### Right to Change Internet Privacy Policy Statement

TheOptionsGuide.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting to our website. By using this site, you signify your agreement with and acceptance of TheOptionsGuide.com's Privacy Policy Statement. If you do not accept this policy, please do not use this site in any way. Your continued use of TheOptionsGuide.com sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes, regardless of whether TheOptionsGuide.com provides you with additional notice of such changes. We recommend that visitors to our website re-visit this Privacy Policy page on occasion to learn of changes to our privacy practices and policies.  
  
---|---
